<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hololive Recycler View</string>
    <string name="member_name">Member Name</string>
    <string name="region">Region</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="youtube_icon">Youtube Icon</string>
    <string name="profile_pics">Profile Pics</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="generation">Generation</string>
    <string name="debut_date">Debut date :</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="linkedin">linkedIn</string>
    <string name="instagram">Instagram</string>
    <string name="github">Github</string>
    <string name="email">fxguntur04@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="fullname">Fx. Guntur Putra Susanto</string>

    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Hoshimachi Suisei</item>
        <item>Shirakami Fubuki</item>
        <item>Sakamata Chloe</item>
        <item>Todoroki Hajime</item>
        <item>Ayunda Risu</item>
        <item>Vestia Zeta</item>
        <item>Kaela Kovalskia</item>
        <item>Hakos Baelz</item>
        <item>Gawr Gura</item>
        <item>Koseki Bijou</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_generation">
        <item>Hololive 0th Generation</item>
        <item>Hololive 1st Generation / Hololive GAMERS</item>
        <item>Hololive 6th Generation / holoX</item>
        <item>Hololive ReGLOSS</item>
        <item>Hololive Indonesia Generation 1</item>
        <item>Hololive Indonesia Generation 3</item>
        <item>Hololive Indonesia Generation 3</item>\
        <item>Hololive English Promise</item>
        <item>Hololive English Myth</item>
        <item>Hololive English Advent</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_debut">
        <item>22 Maret 2018</item>
        <item>1 Juni 2018</item>
        <item>29 November 2021</item>
        <item>10 September 2023</item>
        <item>10 April 2020</item>
        <item>25 March 2022</item>
        <item>26 March 2022</item>
        <item>23 August 2021</item>
        <item>13 September 2020</item>
        <item>30 July 2023</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_region">
        <item>Hololive JP</item>
        <item>Hololive JP</item>
        <item>Hololive JP</item>
        <item>Hololive JP</item>
        <item>Hololive ID</item>
        <item>Hololive ID</item>
        <item>Hololive ID</item>
        <item>Hololive EN</item>
        <item>Hololive EN</item>
        <item>Hololive EN</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>born on March 22 is a cheerful shining Idol and VTuber from Hololive 0th Generation. She is a forever 18, multitalented girl who deeply loves singing and idols, with the dream of one day holding a live concert in Tokyo Budokan. She started out as an independent VTuber and later joined Inonaka Music, a music label under Hololive, before moving officially to Hololive main branch.\nHer name \"Suisei\" translates to \"Comet\" in English, while her last name \"Hoshimachi\" translates to \"City of stars\" in English ,and as such is usually referred to as the comet idol. She is well known for her amazing skills in Tetris, as she is often being called out as the best among VTubers, as well as her psychopathic personality, as shown when she sometimes acts ruthless to others while still giving off a cheerful attitude.\nHer representative emote is a comet.\nHoshimachi Suisei debutted with a modest and earnest personality to do the best in everything she did. She is always cheerful and energetic, rarely showing genuine sadness in streams, and her viewers used to view her as a pure person. She is also hardworking, with her continuing to do VTuber activities even after a year with barely any growth and having her determination to join Hololive even after her first application failed. However, during a stream collaboration with various Hololive members, she was shown to have a remorseless and sociopathic personality while still giving off a carefree attitude when she was killing and hunting out people. Over time, people started to refer to this side of her as \"Psychopath Suisei\" or \"Suicopath\", with her denying it as a side of her.\nShe is particularly sensitive to the topic of chest size as seen in various occasions, and usually threatens her viewers whenever the topic is brought up in the live comments section. On one occasion in a stream with fellow member Shirogane Noel, she shared how when she met with Noel for the first time, she was taken aback by her size.\nShe is a large spender on gacha games, especially the gacha game \"Ensemble Stars\". In a stream with Nijisanji VTuber and friend Inui Toko, she spent an absurd amount of money that shocked both her viewers and Toko, who was also a huge gacha spender on the game. In a quiz stream about gacha games, she was agitated when fellow member Oozora Subaru commented how gacha games were just a waste of money.\nShe usually cares greatly for those close to her, especially her VTuber friends. She has a close relationship with not only Amane Kanata, a fellow member, but also people outside of Hololive, including but not limited to Inui Toko, Lupinus Knightely, Kuon Ran and her real older sister nicknamed Anemachi.</item>

        <item>born October 5 is a fox girl in Hololive 1st Generation and is the leader of hololive GAMERS.\nShe is most known for her short-skit videos posted on Twitter and Youtube. Having an exposure to western and eastern culture memes, she demonstrates it to her audience in some shape or form. She is dubbed as the \"Queen of Memes\", among other related titles that the fans have given her.\nShe plays a variety of games, and often loves to try out any kind of games in any genres. Despite saying that she doesn\'t like horror games, she seems to enjoy streaming and playing them. When she was asked about her skills, she admitted that she had terrible aim in FPS games. She is also known to be a poor driver, having a tendency to mess around with her colleagues to get a laugh out of them as well.\n\nShe is known to be a whale (high spender) in gacha games and any other games with similar aspects, and has shown streaming her rolls in mobile games like FGO and Twisted Wonderland.\n\nIn Japanese, the onomatopoeia for a fox\’s bark is \“kon-kon.\” which sounds like \"corn\". As a result, corn has become Fubuki\’s representative emoji.\n\nShirakami Fubuki debuted with a personality showing off a timid, shy girl that fumbles over her words often, often hiding off the screen and quickly running away when doing embarrassing things. She enjoys talking with people and would enjoy it if you paid attention to her.\n\nThroughout the years, she has gained experience, confidence, the stamina to talk a lot (as demonstrated by her MC-ing the 6 hour long HoloComi event and having sang and MC\'d in Non-Stop Story for the majority of the concert), and the skill to befriend anyone she meets. She is close to her colleagues and tries to help them in any way she can, directly or indirectly, even at the cost of her own self. She shouldered the pillar of the family around the start of Hololive and has kept it up until recently where she has started relying on her own colleagues too.\nFubuki, alongside Hololive 1st Generation Natsuiro Matsuri, has been pushing towards easing the interactions with the sibling-branch Holostars and her fellow Hololive talents. She has collaborated and interacted with the Holostars talents a number of times. Added to this, she often collaborates and messes with Holostar Talent Yukoku Roberu as of recent events, such as bringing bombs to the Robel\'s Bar, or turning him into a bacon during his sleep. She also has a group name with Holostar Talent Aragami Oga called FOXDEMON and has a dynamic of being the lady (Fubuki) of the Shirakami House and its maid (Oga); they often collab and do talk/question streams, or competition streams.\n\nShe is known to be a large spender on gachas in mobile games and has streamed her characters draws before. Some of the viewers get scared with the shockingly high amount of money that she puts into these games. She feels emotional sometimes when she feels impatient or desperate. Examples of this in Animal Crossing are when her Turnip Stocks crash, or when neighbors leave. She also shows her emotions openly when she goes on a 50 draw spree in her mobile games and getting nothing out of it, or her indecisive decisions in shooters leaving her vulnerable. Despite these things happening, she takes them in stride and plays it out as part of her gag.\n\nShe is known to be friends with some indie and other major company/group VTubers and has collaborated with many of them before. They all have a generally good opinion of her, and most of her colleagues sees her as an important figure as well as a good friend. The 1st generation Natsuiro Matsuri has commented in a twitcast that Fubuki is the pillar to Hololive and kept it steady. She is held highly in regards to her reputation and character, and she shoulders the responsibility and weight of people that rely on her.\n\nFubuki can get easily agitated when you call her a cat due to the frequency of people (newbies and fans alike) often mistaking her for a cat. The joke is either done for fun, or purely by accident and she will blurt out \"Neko Janai! Kitsune Jai!(I\'m not a cat! I\'m a fox!)\".\nShe is easily embarrassed by certain topics, as evident by some of her member-only streams, chatting streams, or collaboration interactions. Examples of this are Natsuiro Matsuri and Shiranui Flare teasing and poking at her among others. She has a tendency of feeling wary or anxious when she makes jokes/pranks behind someone\'s back or if someone isn\'t in the presence of her pranks, but she enjoys doing it anyways.</item>

        <item>An intern who acts as a fixer and cleaner for Secret Society holoX.\nCalm and composed at all times, she carries out her orders without so much as batting an eyelid.\nShe loves music and can be found listening to it every chance she gets.\nAnd while she denies it vehemently, she apparently tends to come across as guarded and not very upfront with her thoughts, only letting people get very occasional glimpses into how she really feels.\nShe\'s part of the official Hololive Manga \'holoX MEETing\', along with Takane Lui, Hakui Koyori, La\+ Darknesss, and Kazama Iroha, that\'s being serialized in Shounen Jump Plus.</item>

        <item>Bam! Wow, that actually sounds kinda badass!\n\nA jane-of-all-trades seeking to be the #1 badass in the universe.\nWhy the universe? Why \'badass\'? Nobody knows.\nShe\'s the restless sort and, to no surprise, enjoys physical activities.\nAlso to no surprise, she\'s not good with tools and equipment, meaning she\'s a disaster-class in cooking.\nHer trusty partner Banpen teaches her every day about how to be a badass.\nA jane-of-all-trades seeking to be the #1 badass in the universe.\n\nOn 4 September, after finishing the countdown, hololive DEV_IS YouTube channel introduced the group ReGLOSS along with the music video "Shunkan Heartbeat" revealing the identities of all its members as well as their channels and social media accounts.[3] Hajime also made her first tweet on this date. Hajime\'s teaser video from hololive DEV_IS channel was also uploaded to her personal channel, now fully displaying her face.\n Hajime\'s YouTube channel was created on 21 July 2023, and her Twitter account was also created on this month.\nOn 7 September, hololive DEV_IS\'s YouTube channel uploaded another video this time showing ReGLOSS members actual models and appearances outside of their unified group clothes.\nShe debuted on 10 September 2023 and was the final member to debut. After the stream, she released her first solo cover song "Shokuchuu Shokubutsu" by RIM.\n\n Contrast to her title of "badass", Hajime has a child-like playfulness; this is further characterized by her signature lisp, which is noted by many to make it more difficult to catch her words correctly than that of Sakura Miko\'s however, it becomes a very clear voice when she sings. </item>

        <item>Ayunda Risu is a VTuber from Hololive Indonesia 1st Generation. She is cheerful and likes to play pranks on her friends. She came from a magical forest and met a \"Big Sister\" that takes care of her while she is in human world, and being VTuber is her way to payback her \“Big Sister\”.\n\nRisu has a notably wide vocal-range, even for a singer. At the request of fans she\'s been able to portray a considerable range of identities through voice affectation, even convincing impersonations of other hololive members. Risu\'s fans frequently refer to these identities emulated through voice as \"Risu DLC\'s\", given that they are usually donation requests. Her current most used voices are: \"Risu\" (default), \"Wisu\" (childish), and \"Ayunda\" (deep voice). As shown in her collaboration with Yumeria Nirmala, she also able to perform an ikemen (handsome gentlemen) voice called \"Wisnu\". According to Risu herself, her natural voice is slightly higher than the \"Ayunda\" voice, but still significantly lower than her default pitch. She is able to speak 3 languages: English, Bahasa Indonesia, and Japanese. She is learning Japanese with help from her friends and those around her.\nRisu and her fellow members of Indonesia 1st Generation, Moona Hoshinova and Airani Iofifteen, lived together in a dormitory, though they each had individual rooms. As such, the three have a very close relationship, even sometimes being likened to a family by both themselves and their fans. Frequently, Iofi refers to herself as the father of the group. They collaborate as a trio on the 15th of every month, titled \"Area 15\". This arrangement allowed them to join in on each other\'s streams spontaneously, and streams that began as solo streams have at time become impromptu collaborations.\nAs superchats are not available in Indonesia, Risu has a streamlabs set up alongside superchats for those who want to donate.\nAccording to Risu\'s introduction stream, she claims that she is cheerful, clumsy, as well as a crybaby. She is shown to be determined, although she is bad with ghosts and horror games, she will still play them if her viewers request them, although she will scream and probably cry.\n\nWhile kind, she is very strict on the conduct of the live chat—frequently muting or bonking viewers. On more than one occasion she has taken time out of the stream to lecture misbehaving viewers. She is very concerned with making sure all Risuners are treated equally and does not give preferential treatment in bonking.</item>

        <item>She is the mysterious 7th recruit of The Secret Archive Unit that has a full license to collect virtual data. Despite her being a promising rookie, who is also known as codename V.7, she turns clumsy when things are not going exactly according to the manual.\nIt was initially a lonely mission to infiltrate the virtual world, but now she had found comfort here. Will this mission end up leading her to a new destiny instead?\n\nVestia Zeta, Codename: V.7. An agent from the Secret Archive Unit and a member of Hololive Indonesia 3rd Generation. Debuted on March 25, 2022, able to speak in: Indonesian, English, Japanese and Korean. With the latter two being \"baby level\" according to Zeta in her debut stream. She is currently enjoying her time play, discover and learn new games like Vampire Survivors, Mario Kart, etc. Whilst showing a side of her clumsiness, hence the common use of \"Pon\" by the Zecretaries whenever such moments occurs.\nZeta adopts quite an adorable and curious personality similar to her favorite animal, cats. At the same time she is quite fearless as shown in her Outlast 2 and in late parts of DEVOUR collab w/ Kaela and Kobo. Even refusing to get backseated unless she is really lost, disliking hime-plays and stream snipes like in APEX streams.\nHowever despite her strong side, she also revealed a hint of her soft spot which she stated that she is the kind who easily cries on an especially sad scenes. Of course, we shouldn\'t forget about her various \"Pon\" (clumsiness) moments in most of her streams.\n\nA small QnA session (otherwise described as \"interrogation\") with Zecretaries. This is a series that features \"Would you rather\" questions for zecretaries to vote on, sometimes causing a little mischief by providing her arguments for the choices they have made or gaslighting zecretaries to choose the answer that she has chosen</item>

        <item>After taking over her great blacksmithing teacher\'s forge, she felt a lack of excitement in her life.\nSo, she decided to be free and depart on a journey to find rare smithing materials, one of which was rumored to be under the building of a certain idol group in town.\nShe also loves challenging herself and has a peculiar taste when it comes to foods!\nThis blacksmith is really a hard-working thing. she is really caring and likes to help others but the most favorite thing from her is her randomness. Kaela\'s laugh is often inaudible on stream and Kaela is jokingly called a \"penguin\" by fans, owing to her appearance and her last name\'s similarity to Kowalski, a penguin from the Madagascar series.</item>

        <item>Baelz is loud, unpredictable, and chaotic. Despite this, she seems to have a talent for leading off in discussions and keeping things as orderly as possible, as seen in the first hololive -Council- meeting. Ceres Fauna even described her as a natural born leader, and Baelz eventually embraced the role of \"Leader of -Council\" In contrast to her chaotic nature, she speaks rather fondly of the other -Council- members, and is regarded by them as adorable in turn. Baelz can also be easily flustered if things do not go her way.\n\nSince early after debuting, Baelz is in a chaotic couple relationship with IRyS. They share many tastes and opinions, but also dispute frequently. Consequently, Baelz and IRyS keeping \"divorcing\" and \"remarrying\" depending on their mood.\n\nBaelz doesn\'t know some very popular culture references. Because her knowledge is this limited, Baelz is sometimes called a zoomer, and refered as some kind of opposite to the old boomer Noir Vesper is.\n\nBaelz often recalls her Australian pride. For example, she tries to make the world taste vegemite, a traditional local dish. This dedication led her to open the program \"BAE-GEMITE\" where she invites holomems tasting it.\n\nHakos Baelz\'s debut was originally scheduled for 22 August, by Japan time. A -Council- group collaboration on her channel was tentatively scheduled two hours later. However, the -Council- debuts were postponed for 24 hours due to unspecified technical issues, which members jokingly blamed on the \"EN curse\" a perceived tendency for hololive English members to suffer from unexpected technical problems.[20] The debuts were rescheduled at the same time on Sunday 22 August (US/Europe time) or Monday 23 August (Japan time).</item>

        <item>Gura is friendly and readily likeable, and often amuses her viewers with foolish antics. She has no sense of direction, often misspells and mispronounces words, has trouble remembering her own age, and consistently fails to solve basic math problems, leading viewers to affectionately call her a \"dum shark\". Memorably, one viewer declared that \"Gura has a heart of gold and a head of bone.\"\nShe can also be lazy at times. She often forgets about perishable items until they start to rot, and eats baby food \"because you don\’t have to cook it [or] chew on it.\"\nHowever, despite her poor math and spelling skills, Gura is quick-witted, clever, and has vast knowledge of Shark Facts. When questioned on why she was not \"boing boing\" she excused it by claiming that she was \"hydrodynamic.\" Her skill with fast-paced rhythm games is exceptional, and she is highly ambitious. She also occasionally makes lewd jokes, and is familiar with modern meme culture, which she references often.\n\nGawr Gura is very short, reaching around 141 cm (4\’7\"). She has a slim body type. She has white, light silver-like hair with baby blue and cobalt blue strands, along with short pigtails on either side of her head, tied with diamond-shaped, shark-faced hair ties. She has cyan pupils, and sharp, shark-like teeth. She can wear a dark cerulean-blue hood in the shape of a shark\’s head.\nShe wears an oversized, dark cerulean-blue hoodie that fades into white on her arm sleeves and hem, two yellow strings in the shape of an \"x\" that connect the front part of her white hoodie hood, a shark mouth designed on her hoodie waist with a zipper, gray hoodie drawstrings with two black circles on each of them, and two pockets on the left and right sides of her hoodie waist with white fish bone designs on them.\nShe also wears a gray shirt under her hoodie. She wears dark blue socks, white shoes with pale baby blue shoe tongues, black shoelaces, gray velcro patches on the vamps, and thick, black soles. She wields a sapphire-blue trident and has a cyan shark tail. The upper lobe of Gura\’s caudal fin, the top part of her tail, is sewn up with gray stitches because of a rock that fell on it while she was in a deep sea trench. The lower lobe of Gura\’s caudal fin, the bottom part of her tail, has three bite marks, which she forgot the cause of.</item>

        <item>\”I hope you\’ll feel my radiance!\” Formed from the crystallization of all forms of human emotion, Koseki Bijou is \”The Jewel of Emotions.\” Over years and years, emotions of beauty and filth alike have woven into her under immense pressure, resulting in an unmatched brilliance.\nHer ancient, mystic brilliance caused strife between the masses of the greedy, who fought over ownership of her. This led to her being imprisoned in secrecy, far from the reach of humans.\nIt seems as though when she encounters people, and particularly their good emotions, her radiance shines even brighter.\n\nShe has long, silvery-purple hair with darker purple eyes. She has a dark purple crown. She has metallic pink wings with jewels hanging off her body.\n\nFollowing the debut of hololive English second generation -Council-, hololive English announced a permanent English language audition page on 30 December 2021. An update to the audition page on 7 September 2022 sparked speculation of an upcoming English third generation.\nBijou first discovered hololive from YouTube clips after the -Myth- debuts in 2020. She was inspired to audition for hololive, despite having no experience streaming at that time. Despite initially being rejected, she decided to focus all her efforts on her goal of joining. She applied three times before she was successful.\nAt the audition, Bijou demonstrated her technical, gameplay and creative talent by playing her own fan-made mod of Undertale, defeating the boss Sans, who she had replaced with Mori Calliope. Later, she recalls that when she learned she had been selected to join hololive, she was listening to the song I Really Want to Stay at Your House from the game Cyberpunk 2077.\nKoseki Bijou\’s YouTube and Twitter accounts were originally created on 11 May 2023, although they contained no content at this point.\nThe third generation of hololive English, -Advent-, was first teased on the hololive English Twitter account with a short video on 22 July 2023. This was followed by another teaser video on 23 July, showing five new characters.\nOn 25 July, the hololive English YouTube channel posted a video titled Wanted!, revealing the five members of -Advent- and announcing their upcoming debuts. At the same time, Bijou also posted a short teaser video on her YouTube channel and made her first tweet.\nAll -Advent- members\’ YouTube channels reached 100,000 subscribers within twelve hours of the announcement.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_photo">
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/1/1f/Hoshimachi_Suisei_-_Portrait_04.png/420px-Hoshimachi_Suisei_-_Portrait_04.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/c/c6/Shirakami_Fubuki_-_Portrait_01.png/435px-Shirakami_Fubuki_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/6/61/Sakamata_Chloe_-_Portrait_01.png/420px-Sakamata_Chloe_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/1/18/Todoroki_Hajime_-_Portrait_01.png/450px-Todoroki_Hajime_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/f/fe/Ayunda_Risu_-_Portrait_01.png/435px-Ayunda_Risu_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/4/4e/Vestia_Zeta_-_Portrait_01.png/450px-Vestia_Zeta_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/b/b5/Kaela_Kovalskia_-_Portrait_01.png/450px-Kaela_Kovalskia_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/1/16/Hakos_Baelz_-_Portrait_01.png/420px-Hakos_Baelz_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/6/69/Gawr_Gura_-_Portrait_01.png/435px-Gawr_Gura_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
        <item>https://static.miraheze.org/hololivewiki/thumb/9/9f/Koseki_Bijou_-_Portrait_01.png/450px-Koseki_Bijou_-_Portrait_01.png</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>